{
    "subject": "resource/Mulligan's_Stew",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Mulligan's Stew",
    "human_readable": "The name of Mulligan's Stew is Mulligan's Stew.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9835923910140991,
            "question": "What is the name of Mulligan's Stew?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.967924177646637,
            "question": "Is Mulligan's Stew a dish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9374265074729919,
            "question": "Does Mulligan's Stew have a unique name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9356162548065186,
            "question": "Is Mulligan's Stew a traditional dish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9353488683700562,
            "question": "Is Mulligan's Stew a popular dish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9146075248718262,
            "question": "What does the name 'Mulligan's Stew' suggest about its origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8799799084663391,
            "question": "What kind of food is Mulligan's Stew likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8617715239524841,
            "question": "Where might someone find a recipe for Mulligan's Stew?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8379607200622559,
            "question": "Are there different variations of Mulligan's Stew?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7875360250473022,
            "question": "Could someone order Mulligan's Stew at a restaurant?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Mulligan's Stew is Mulligan's Stew.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1480_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there different variations of Mulligan's Stew?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1480_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might someone find a recipe for Mulligan's Stew?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1480_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of food is Mulligan's Stew likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1480_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1480_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1480_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1480_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1480_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1480_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1480_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1480_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1480_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1480_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1480_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about \"Mulligan Stew\" and confirm that it is indeed called by that name. Therefore, the statement \"The name of Mulligan's Stew is Mulligan's Stew\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The name \"Mulligan Stew\" is actually a given name, not the name of the dish itself.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}